export default [
	{
		id: "1",
		title: "this is title #1",
		description: "this is description #1",
		cards: [
			{ front: "front #1", back: "back #1", },
			{ front: "front #2", back: "back #2", },
			{ front: "front #3", back: "back #3", },
		],
	},
	{
		"id": "2",
		title: "this is title #2",
		description: "this is description #2",
		cards: [
			{ front: "front #1", back: "back #1", },
			{ front: "front #2", back: "back #2", },
			{ front: "front #3", back: "back #3", },
			{ front: "front #4", back: "back #4", },
			{ front: "front #4", back: "back #4", },
			{ front: "front #4", back: "back #4", },
			{ front: "front #4", back: "back #4", },
		],
	},
]
